

SARNENDU KARMAKAR Senior Process Associate

CUSTOMER SERVICE PROFESSIONAL

OBJECTIVE

Detail-oriented Medical Billing Specialist with 5 years of experience managing Medical Insurance and Patient Claim Payments. A team player with a positive and winning attitude and a passion for service looking to make a significant contribution to your company.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Process Associate

Neemtree Consultants Pvt. Ltd.

(September 2020 - Present)

Responsibilities:

- Denial posting with denial codes in respective patients' accounts
- Posting payments according to ERA, EFT and EOB according to Payment Protocol in patients' accounts
- Responsible for month end and reconcile of particular practices.
- Process refund as per EOB.
- Work on AR- follow up details.
- Mail solving, which are forwarded by client.

Process Associate

Medfin India PVT LTD (A Cognizant Company)

(December 2016 - September 2020)

Responsibilities:

- Reporting payment amount as per bank websites
- Download ERA, EFT and EOB files as per reported deposit log
- Post payment in respective account and reconcile monthly log
- Mail solving, which are forwarded by client
- Preparing transfer log to submit transfer amount to client

EDUCATION

M.Sc (Anthropology) West Bengal State University (May 2013 - August 2015)

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Won thrice spotlight certificate in Medfin India PVT LTD (A Cognizant Company) for highest quarterly production
- Have recognized for always being a consistent performer in my current organization.

DATE OF BIRTH

12th December 1992

CONTACTDETAILS

405/9 North Nilachal, Birati, Kolkata - 700134

1+918981428026

Sarnendukarmakar5@gmail.com

SKILLS

Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, and PowerPoint)
V&H look up

LANGUAGES

English (Professional) Hindi (Proficient) Bengali (Native)

INTERESTS

Reading Gardening Listening Audio Story